learnfinancialeducation.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy

This website respects your privacy and is committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at [http://learnfinancialeducation.com](http://learnfinancialeducation.com/). The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this blog.

Like most standard website servers, this blog uses log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**E-mail Subscription**  
If a user wants to subscribe to my blog via e-mail (you can see at the right side bar), this blog requires for contact information such as name and/or email address. Out of respect for the users’ privacy, a way to opt-out of these feature is provided.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. This site uses cookies for tracking visitors’ activity. Some of my business partners use cookies on our site such as our advertisers. However, this blog has no access or control over these cookies.

**Links**  
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our visitors and users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personal information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this site.

**Advertisers**  
We use advertisement companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. I work with the following ad companies: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding my privacy policy, please contact me by sending email to: _**gil@learnfinancialeducation.com**_.   Thanks!
